<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="maps.xsl" ?>
<Mulitplayer-Maps xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="maps.xsd">
	<map2>
	
	

	
	<adrift>
	ADRIFT - is a map in Halo 4. Although this CAA mining vessel was 
	refitted as an ordnance transport, damage sustained during the 
	Battle of Kholo has condemned it to an inescapable slide down 
	the gravity well of a gas giant. On board, its automated systems
	continue unabated, their operations executed in eerie futility 
	as they drift ever-closer to destruction.
	</adrift>
	
	</map2>
	
	<map3>
	
	
	
	
	<exile>
	EXILE - is an asymmetrical, large vehicle based map, that offers
	a wide variety of gametypes, from CTF to Regicide. it has two 
	main canyons, but they are thoroughly interconnnected.
	</exile>
	
	</map3>
	
	<map4>
	
	

	
	<haven>
	HAVEN - is a multiplayer map in Halo 4 that rests high above 
	Requiem's surface. Harmonic-resonance platforms appear to 
	facilitate the monitoring and management of the shield world's
	solar preservation system. These elaborate machines enable 
	artificial planets to support their immense populations of 
	indigenous life.
	</haven>
	
	</map4>
	
	<map5>
	
	
	
	<longbow>
	LONGBOW is a multiplayer map in Halo 4 for the Wargames Game mode. 
	The frigid climate and unique gravitational conditions of Concord's
	northern polar region provide an optimal perch for Longbow Station's 
	channel-based mass drivers. Before the Covenant War, the UEG launched 
	deep space monitoring relays from here in an effort to study far-flung
	star systems.
	</longbow>
	
	</map5>
	
	<map6>
	
	
	<meltdown>
	MELTDOWN - 343 Industries Lead Multiplayer Level Designer Kynan Pearson takes 
	IGN editor Ryan McCaffrey on a guided tour of "Meltdown," a large-scale,
	vehicle friendly map and one of ten core Halo 4 multiplayer maps.
	</meltdown>
	
	</map6>
	
	<map7>
	

	
	<ragnarok>
	RAGNAROK -  is a multiplayer map in Halo 4 and a remake of Valhalla, 
	a multiplayer map from Halo 3. The only major differences between 
	the two maps are the graphics and default weapon layout.
	Ragnarok is the first of Halo 4's maps to feature a Mantis by default.
	</ragnarok>
	
	</map7>
	
	<map8>
	

	
	<solace>
	SOLACE - is a multiplayer map in Halo 4. Solace is a symmetrical, 
	medium-small, three teered competitive map that will be included
	in the at launch package.It offers a variety of gameplay, from 
	CTF to regicide.
	</solace>
	
	</map8>
	
	<map9>
	
	
	
	<vortex>
	VORTEX - is a large, vehicle-heavy multiplayer
	map designed for bigger-team battles. It is the
	only Halo 4 map with a Rocket Warthog on it by default.
	</vortex>
	
	
	</map9>
	</Mulitplayer-Maps>